Guide to the Stanford University Clippings Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University clippings collection
1891-1945
SC0015
Stanford University. Office of the President
14 Linear feet (112 volumes)
Scrapbooks of newspaper clippings collected by the staff of the President's Office pertaining to University events and interests.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Scrapbooks of newspaper clippings collected by the staff of the President's Office pertaining to University events and interests.
Access Terms
Branner, John Casper, 1850-1922.; Bryan, William Jennings, 1860-1925; Jordan, David Starr, 1851-1931; Ross, Edward Alsworth, 1866-1951.; Stanford University. Office of the President; Stanford, Jane Lathrop, 1828-1905.; Stanford, Leland, 1824-1893.; Tresidder, Donald Bertrand, 1894-1948; Wilbur, Ray L., (Ray Lyman), 1875-1949; Newsclippings.; Scrapbooks
Collection Contents
- Papers
  - Volume 1, 1891 March - 1892 February
  - Volume 2, 1892 February - 1893 February
  - Volume 3, 1893 February - 1893 June
  - Volume 4, 1893 June - 1894 July
  - Volume 5, 1894 September - 1897 January
  - Volume 6, 1897 January - July
  - Volume 7, 1897 January - 1898 February
  - Volume 8, 1898 February - November
  - Volume 9, 1898 November - 1899 March
  - Special 9A: May 1898 -- March 1900 (Jordan and War. Includes pamphlets and at least one letter from William Jennings Bryan.), 1898 May - 1900 March
  - Volume 10, 1899 March - June
  - Volume 11, 1900 June - September
  - Volume 12, 1899 October - 1900 March
  - Volume 13, 1900 March - September
  - Special 13A: November 1900 -- March 1901 (Ross Affair), 1900 November - 1901 March
  - Volume 14, 1900 September - 1901 January
  - Volume 15, 1901 January - July
  - Volume 16, 1901 August - 1902 February
  - Volume 17, 1902 February - September
  - Volume 18, 1902 October - 1903 April
  - Volume 19 (Ross Affair), 1901 March
  - Volume 20, 1903 April - 1904 May
  - Volume 21, 1904 May - October
  - Volume 22, 1904 November - 1905 January
  - Volume 23, 1905 February - March
  - Volume 24, 1905 February - May
  - Volume 25 (Mrs. Stanford's death), 1905 March - May
  - Volume 26, 1905 May - October
  - Volume 27, 1905 October - December
  - Volume 28, 1905 December - 1906 March
  - Volume 29, 1906 March - June
  - Volume 30, 1906 June - December
  - Volume 31, 1906 December - 1907 March
  - Volume 32, 1907 March - June
  - Volume 33, 1907 June - February 1908
  - Volume 34, 1908 February - December
  - Volume 35, 1909 January - 1911 February
  - Volume 36, 1911 February - 1912 April
  - Volume 37, 1912 May - 1914 August
  - Volume 38, 1912 March - 1914 December
  - Volume 39, 1915 January - 1916 September
  - Volume 40, 1916 September - 1917 September
  - Volume 41, 1917 September - 1919 February
  - Volume 42, 1919 February - November
  - Volume 43, 1919 November - 1920 June
  - Volume 44, 1920 June - 1921 February
  - Volume 45, 1921 February - 1922 January
  - Volume 46, 1922 January - June
  - Volume 47, 1922 June - November
  - Volume 48, 1922 November - 1923 March
  - Volume 49, 1923 March - July
  - Volume 50, 1923 August - 1924 January
  - Volume 51, 1924 January - 1924 June
  - Volume 52, 1924 June - December
  - Volume 53, 1925 January - April
  - Volume 54, 1925 May - December
  - Volume 55, 1926
  - Volume 56, 1927
  - Volume 57, 1928 January - June
  - Volume 58, 1928 July - December
  - Volume 59, 1929 January - March
  - Volume 60, 1929 April - December
  - Volume 61, 1930
  - Volume 62, 1931 January - July
  - Volume 63, 1931 August - December
  - Volume 64, 1932 January - June
  - Volume 65, 1932 July - December
  - Volume 66, 1932 June - December
  - Volume 67, 1933 January - April
  - Volume 68, 1933 May - August
  - Volume 69, 1933 September - December
  - Volume 70
  - Volume 71, 1934 January - April
  - Volume 72, 1934 May - August
  - Volume 73, 1934 October - December
  - Volume 74, 1935 January - June
  - Volume 75, 1935 July - September
  - Volume 76, 1935 October - December
  - Volume 77, 1936 May - August
  - Volume 78, 1936 January - April
  - Volume 79, 1936 September - December
  - Volume 80, 1937 January - April
  - Volume 81, 1937 May - August
  - Volume 82, 1937 September - December
  - Volume 83, 1938 January - February
  - Volume 84, 1938 March - May
  - Volume 85, 1938 June - July
  - Volume 86, 1938 September - November
  - Volume 87: R. L. Wilbur, 1938
  - Volume 88, 1938 December - 1939 Feburary
  - Volume 89, 1939 March - May
  - Volume 90, 1939 June - July
  - Volume 91, 1939 August - October
  - Volume 92, 1939 November - December
  - Volume 93, 1939
  - Volume 94, 1940 January - March
  - Volume 95, 1940 April - May
  - Volume 96, 1940 June - July
  - Volume 97, 1940 August - September
  - Volume 98, 1940 October - November
  - Volume 99, 1940 December - 1941 February
  - Volume 100, 1941 December - 1942 April
  - Volume 101, 1942 May - November
  - Volume 102, 1941 October - 1942 June
  - Volume 103, 1941 March - April
  - Volume 104, 1941 May - June
  - Volume 105, 1941 July - September
  - Volume 106, 1943 January - March
  - Volume 107, 1943 April - August
  - Volume 108, 1943
  - Volume 109, 1944
  - Volume 110, 1945 January - May